* About WordPress

* Search

    [

 ](https://traderonthestreet.com/)

Cart
----

No products in the cart.

    [

 ](https://traderonthestreet.com/)

Cart
----

No products in the cart.

Search for: 

  [

 ](https://traderonthestreet.com/)

* * *

Privacy Policy for Trader On The Street

 Languages

Privacy Policy
==============

Last Updated: May 13, 2023

1\. Introduction
----------------

Trader on the Street, LLC ("we", "our", or "us") respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. This policy describes:

* The types of information we may collect or that you may provide when you visit the website www.traderonthestreet.com (our "Website").
    
* Our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

2\. Contact Information
-----------------------

For any queries or concerns about our use of your personal data, please send an email to: [legal@traderonthestreet.com](mailto:legal@traderonthestreet.com)

3\. Purpose for Data Usage
--------------------------

We use your data for promotional purposes, marketing, business decision-making, and analytics.

4\. Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
-------------------------------------------

We use cookies and other tracking technologies to improve and personalize your experience on our Website, to show you targeted advertising, to analyze our Website traffic, and to understand where our visitors come from.

5\. The Personal Information We Collect
---------------------------------------

We may collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including:

* Cookies: Cookies are bits of software that are placed on your computer hard drive when you visit certain Trader on the Street financial and media products. We use cookies to help us identify product features in which you may have the greatest interest. Cookies may enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are using a particular product. Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of all the product features.
    
* Personal identification information: Name, email address, phone number.
    
* Technical data: IP address, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform, and other technology on the devices you use to access this Website.
    
* Usage data: Information about how you use our Website, products, and services.
    
* Marketing and Communications data: Your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties and your communication preferences.
    
* Personally, identifiable information that you knowingly choose to disclose, which is collected on an individual basis General user information that does not contain personally identifiable information, which is collected on an aggregate basis as you browse our Websites. In some cases, if you choose not to provide us with requested information, you may not be able to access all of our Websites’ content or services.
    
* Trader on the Street relationship data: This is data we obtain from our interactions with you, and may include details of the calls you have made to our sales or support, visits made to you by our staff, Trader on the Street marketing materials you have received, your email communication with our staff, data about your preferred activities for marketing events or the Trader on the Street events you have attended. Calls made to Trader on the Street may be monitored and recorded for training and review processes.
    
* Credit card data: If you are subscribing to our products as an individual, we collect your credit card information in order to maintain your services.
    
* Product usage data: This is data we obtain about your usage of Trader on the Street products and may include when and which products you have used and the content and functionality you have used in those products.
    
* Subscription data: This is data we obtain from our interactions with you and may include the products or data sets to which you subscribe or which you are enabled to access.
    
* Surveys, competitions, prize draws: This is data you may provide when you participate in our competitions, prize draws or surveys.

6\. Legal Basis for Processing Personal Information
---------------------------------------------------

Our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described above depends on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it. However, we will normally collect personal information from you only:

* Where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you;
    
* Where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your rights;
    
* Where we have your consent to do so.

7\. Sharing of Personal Information
-----------------------------------

We may share your personal data with third-party service providers to facilitate our services, to provide the service on our behalf, to perform service-related activities or to assist us in analyzing how our service is used. These third parties have access to your personal data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

8\. User Privacy Rights
-----------------------

In accordance with GDPR and CalOPPA, users have the following rights:

* The right to access: You have the right to request copies of your personal data.
    
* The right to rectification: You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request us to complete information you believe is incomplete.
    
* The right to erasure: You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.
    
* The right to restrict processing: You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.
    
* The right to object to processing: You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.
    
* The right to data portability: You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.

9\. How to Exercise Your Privacy Rights
---------------------------------------

To exercise any of your rights, please contact our Compliance Department at [legal@traderonthestreet.com](mailto:legal@traderonthestreet.com). We will respond to your request within one month of receiving it.

10\. Changes to Our Privacy Policy
----------------------------------

We reserve the right to amend this policy at any time.

COPYRIGHT POLICY
================

It is the policy of Trader on the Street to limit access to our Service and terminate the accounts of users who infringe the intellectual property rights of others, including but not limited to those users who are repeat infringers or are repeatedly charged with infringement.

If you believe that anything on our Service infringes any copyright that you own or control, you may notify our Designated Agent. Please see 17 U.S.C. § 512(c)(3) for the requirements of a proper notification.

Please note that if you knowingly misrepresent that any activity or material on our Service is infringing, you may be liable for any damages, including costs and attorneys’ fees, incurred by us or the alleged infringer. You may submit a proper notification to our Designated Agent using the following contact information:

**Designated Agent:** Legal Agent

**Address:** 383 W Lakeview Rd, Lindon, UT 84042

**Email:** [legal@traderonthestreet.com](mailto:legal@traderonthestreet.com)

This copyright policy and our designated agent contact information are provided pursuant to 17 U.S.C. § 512(i)(1)(A) and 17 U.S.C. § 512(c)(2). As used herein, the term “Service” has the meaning given in our Terms of Use, available at [https://traderonthestreet.com/terms-of-service](https://traderonthestreet.com/terms-of-service), and the terms \`\`Trader on the Street”, “we”, “us”, “our” or similar refer to Trader on the Street, LLC and its affiliated companies and its/their successors and assigns.

Contact Us
==========

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, You can contact us:

* By visiting this page on our website: [https://traderonthestreet.com/contact-us/](https://traderonthestreet.com/contact-us/)

  [

 ](https://traderonthestreet.com/)

* 383 W Lakeview Rd  
    Lindon, UT 84042

#### Resources

#### LEGAL

TRADERONTHESTREET © All rights reserved

Online Bootcamp

Please login to access this form!

Pin

Submit

×
